The Future is a drama, fantasy, romance film directed by Miranda July.
When a couple decides to adopt a stray cat their perspective on life changes radically, literally
altering the course of time and space and testing their faith in each other and themselves.
Sophie / Paw-Paw (voice), played by Miranda July.
Jason, played by Hamish Linklater.
Marshall, played by David Warshofsky.
Gabriella, played by Isabella Acres.
Dance Studio Receptionist, played by Angela Trimbur.
Animal Shelter Receptionist, played by Mary Passeri.
The Future is a 2011 drama film written, directed by, and starring Miranda July.
The Future made its world premiere at the 2011 Sundance Film Festival.
The film was nominated for the Golden Bear at the 61st
Berlin International Film Festival.
The tone is emotional.